John Patrick Resurreccion

Software Developer

 $\underline{+63\ 956\ 672\ 3445} \cdot \underline{patrickjohn.resurreccion18@gmail.com} \cdot \underline{https://www.linkedin.com/in/john-patrick-resurreccion-5b5314213/}$

Catanauan, Quezon

SUMMARY

Experienced building web apps with React.js and create new features based on the clients requirements. Participated in sprint planning, daily stand ups, demo and retrospective. Has a strong value of time and dedication for assigned tickets in a sprint. Participated also on collaboration between designers, QA's and backend developers for the planning and building the desired output for the project.

SKILLS / KEY COMPETENCIES

Web Front End Programming Testing and Maintenance Mobile App Development Reporting and presenting with client Critical thinking skills Excellent communication skills Strong interpersonal skills Proactive and self-motivated Database Programming

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Zeniark Philippines Consulting Corp Jr. React Developer

April 2023 - Present

 $Technologies - Typescript \cdot ReactJS \cdot NextJS \cdot Zod/Yup \cdot RTK \ Query \cdot TanStack \cdot Ant \ Design \cdot Mantine \ UI + Control of the Control of t$

- Created responsive ReactJS and/or NextJS web components with Ant Design to provide better user interface and interaction
- Developed UI based on the design from Figma and/or Sketch including multiple features based on the tasks requirements for websites and/or web apps
- Coordination with the Backend, QA, fellow Front End, Team Lead and Project Manager to ensure the productive work
- Participate DSM's, sprint planning, ticket assigning, retrospective and more
- Perform code review and knowledge transfer with the team
- Integrate API. Perform HTTP requests such as GET, POST, PATCH, PUT and DELETE using RTK Query and TanStack Query

ISBX Philippines, Inc Fullstack Developer

Aug 2022 - Feb 2023

- $Technologies Typescript \cdot ReactJS/React\ Native \cdot NextJS \cdot NestJS \cdot PostgreSQL \cdot Formik \cdot Yup \cdot Material\ UI$
- Developed Web Application and Mobile Application for multiple clients
- Participate DSM's, sprint planning, ticket assigning, retrospective and more
- Created Unit Testing and End to End Testing using Jest to ensure each features and endpoints are working as expected
- · Created API to serve data to the client side using NestJS as backend and PostgreSQL as database
- Added different validations based on each endpoints and data
- · Integrate different third party packages to achieve specific goals based on the requirements

EDUCATION & CERTIFICATIONS

STI College Lucena

BS in Information Technology 2018 - 2022

Bondoc Peninsula Agricultural High School

2012 - 2018

EXTRACURRICULAR ACTIVITIES

EPAS President

Bondoc Peninsula Agricultural High School